Where is
that
[Music]
[Praise]
Hello friends,
in today's video of investment,
friends are going to talk about the life
insurance sector. 31 friends is
ICICI Lombard General Insurance,
second is Top 200, HDFC Life and spotted
friends SBI Life, ICICI HDFC,
friends
subscribe, big players in the Indian market,
friends and all three which are
trading on the topic, from here we could have made money,
how should the inter-state be
subscribed, friends,
it was very good,
see here friends, I
connected an iron 20 with this, friends,
and see there that the 50% treatment at
1240, it has been trying to fold it for the last two decades,
friends, this stop, so
now from here friends,
before it goes up further, friends, take out this statement,
note the level of 1240, it is a 50
% retracement, now here it is,
friends, and we had made this eye, then
how much did our replacement go around, friends,
replacement of 38.2%, and
friends, I tried to break the fast to fold it,
but then  After that, it went up
and then again a paste is made that
touches the option of 22 candle, so there is a
full chance that the same
situation will remain here, it will form two wicket candles and
we will get a good bounce back. This is Vijay's
friends, what should we do to make money for the media, so
friends,
now on the Delhi chart, why not
see this
continuous level of 1240, friends, try to understand friends,
22nd friends, see one to
three inches here, see
one to three inches here, 1241
subscribe friends,
subscribe here friends,
above this, friends, 1200, so
friends, here you reduce it for 10 to 15 minutes,
friends,
now secondly, friends, this
moving average of various highs and lows,
friends, is forming near it, so subscribe for one, you can subscribe for the
whole, and we can
stand at the appointed place, 1240,
if you want to time it well, then you can do it for 15 minutes more,
it is known for long term investment,
so I would advise selling this one.
This is it friends, that's why friends, let's talk about the
second friends, there is a
full possibility of a pit coming above the tremendous in life, friends, so look here friends,
two, there is another sweet of this, our live
time itself, that is, the third of September 2001, its
replacement of 16108 came at 506, right there
friends, that Ajay and weave what a
tremendous thing, friends, he has come, even you will
see after licking Delhi, friends, the entire
replacement has come around fifty percent,
ICC Lombard General Insurance
and friends, both have come around fifty percent,
it had broken 60 percent,
completed the replacement in a single day
and saw its 20 moving average, which
cannot stay very far from there, I have
told you many times, and here also friends,
this Stark started on
Thursday and came back by mouse back, so
now the level of five-seven, this is our level,
you can run by doing that problem, right now
you can keep a stoploss of 506 for the long term
and it is very good friends,
you can get momentum here, it can become even faster,
friends  Friends, in this topic,
HDFC is a very good
company and has given very good returns.
Already friends, let's talk about SBI Life.
This Life is
very good friends and has a
very strong price of
1520 3.6 percent, which is
moving around the same level, right after the slow top
and till this level,
delete the weekly chart, if we
go above it, then the level here is a
very big level, friends, friends, which was a
continuous top business, friends, it went
up by folding a lot of the world,
subscribe to the top level and
because of this, people made on it and it is trying to go up,
so near 10
subscribers,
it is
now used to cross here,
friends,
subscribe, then how far did it go,
friends, so you see what happens,
why not, so see this, it is very
good friends, you got this, once it
crosses it positively, then
you can get a huge rally, in the coming time,
chilli and here I was very far away,
friends, taking between  Price increase, then
remember one thing friends, you must have seen 20 in the past, it went
away from there, then it touched from there,
friends, it will come back again, friends, it is
entered here, so once a complement
crosses, then you can get a huge
momentum and take a stoploss of 1010, it will
not be a very good dream defect
and it has the potential to give you very good returns in the coming time,
so friends, that's all for today's video,
if you liked the video then
like, share,
subscribe, see you
in the next video, till then thank you and this
saree does not have a professional courier combination,
now this is finance investment advice,
you can do tennis in it, thank you,
thank you very much friends, thank you